let questions =[
    {
        numb:1,
        question: "What is your skin type?",
        answer: "c. Combination",
        options: [
            "a. Oily",
            "b. Dry",
            "c. Combination",
            "d. Normal",   

        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question: "How sensitive is your skin?",
        answer: "b. Sensitive",
        options: [
            "a. Very sensitive",
            "b. Sensitive",
            "c. Normal",
            "d. Not sensitive"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question: "Do you have any specific skin concerns? (Select all that apply)",
        answer: "b. Aging",
        options: [
            "a. Acne",
            "b. Aging",
            "c. Dark spots",
            "d. Pores",
            "e. Redness"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question: "How often do you experience breakouts?",
        answer: "a. Rarely",
        options: [
            "a. Rarely",
            "b. Occasionally",
            "c. Frequently",
            "d. Constantly"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question: "How would you describe your current skincare routine? (Select the most applicable)",
        answer: "d. I don't have a routine",
        options: [
            "a. Minimalist",
            "b. Basic",
            "c. Comprehensive",
            "d. I don't have a routine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question: "Are you looking for products with natural or synthetic ingredients?",
        answer: "c. No preference",
        options: [
            "a. Natural",
            "b. Synthetic",
            "c. No preference"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question: "Do you spend a significant amount of time in the sun?",
        answer: "b. Occasionally",
        options: [
            "a. Yes, often",
            "b. Occasionally",
            "c. Rarely",
            "d. No, never"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question: "What is your age group?",
        answer: "b. 25-34",
        options: [
            "a. 18-24",
            "b. 25-34",
            "c. 35-44",
            "d. 45+"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question: "How much time are you willing to dedicate to your skincare routine each day?",
        answer: "a. Less than 5 minutes",
        options: [
            "a. Less than 5 minutes",
            "b. 5-10 minutes",
            "c. 10-20 minutes",
            "d. More than 20 minutes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question: "Are you currently using any specific skincare products or brands? If yes, please specify.",
        answer: "b. 5-10 minutes",
        options: [
            "a. Less than 5 minutes",
            "b. 5-10 minutes",
            "c. 10-20 minutes",
            "d. More than 20 minutes"
        ]
    }  
];

